question_data = [
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Sports",
                                                "question": "Wilt Chamberlain scored his infamous 100-point-game against the New York Knicks in 1962.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                                  "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                                                  "question": "Soulja Boy&#039;s &#039;Crank That&#039; won a Grammy for Best Rap Song in 2007.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                                  "category": "Science: Mathematics",
                                                  "question": "A &#039;Millinillion&#039; is a real number.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                                  "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
                                                  "question": "Night on Bald Mountain was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney&#039;s 1940&#039;s film Fantasia.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Animals",
                                                  "question": "You can tell the age of a ladybird by counting the spots on his back.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Art",
                                                  "question": "Venus of Willendorf is one of the earliest works of art, depicting the planets Mars and Venus embrace in the heavens at night.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                                  "category": "Entertainment: Television",
                                                  "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons respect William Shakespeare, they even suspect him having a Klingon lineage.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                                  "category": "Science: Computers",
                                                  "question": "It&#039;s not possible to format a write-protected DVD-R Hard Disk.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                                  "category": "General Knowledge",
                                                  "question": "Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                                  "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                                                  "question": "EDM label Monstercat signs tracks instead of artists.",
                                                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
